(Howard:)This is her
last brisket.
last meatloaf.
(Howard:)This is her last...
(Howard:)I have no idea
what this is, but...
(Howard:)it's the last one.
(Raj:)Everything okay?
(Sheldon:)No.
(Howard:)All Ma's food is
gonna be ruined.
(Bernadette:)Well, why don't we take it home
and put it in our freezer?
(Raj:)You don't want
to do that.
(Raj:)Refreezing not only
removes moisture,
(Raj:)but it creates ice crystals
in the fibers of the meat
(Raj:)that can compromise
its taste and texture.
(Raj:)What? I saw a teachable moment.
(Raj:)I dropped some culinary science.
(Bernadette:)What should we do?
(Howard:)I'll tell you exactly
what we're gonna do.
(Howard:)We're gonna eat it.
There's, like, 20 pounds
of food in there.
(Howard:)All you said
(Howard:)was I had to get rid of things.
(Howard:)You didn't say they couldn't
pass through my colon first.
(Bernadette:)Howie...
(Raj:)Okay.
(Howard:)Then how about this?
(Howard:)Let's invite everyone
over to dinner.